不准祈求  不准装可怜
No begging. No begging.
斯黛拉  你让我心碎了
Stella, you're breaking my heart here.
让你心碎的是香肠和培根
What's breaking your heart is that sausage and bacon.
你就不能只吃一种吗
Can't you just pick one?
别担心  我会在高尔夫球场上
Don't worry. I'm gonna burn it off
消耗掉热量的
on the golf course.
怎么消耗  杰
How, Jay?
坐在高尔夫球车上消耗
By riding the little cart
还是靠把球踢回场内
or by kicking the ball back into play?
拿着  我要带乔・弗汉希欧去公园
Here. I'm gonna take Joe Fulgencio to the park.
你能去超市买点东西吗
Can you please stop by the grocery store?
为什么不让保姆去
Why doesn't the nanny do this?
你逗我呢吧
You got to be kidding me!
歌洛莉亚已经开除五个保姆了
Gloria has fired five nannies.
我不希望我家里有别的女人
I don't like another woman in my house.
我要当唯一的明星
I want to be the star.
明星都有保姆
Stars have nannies.
你知道这里面多少有曼尼的错
You know that some of this is Manny's fault.
曼尼
Manny!
玛丽  你今天晚餐想做什么
So, Marie, what do you feel like doing for dinner tonight?
你晚上就吃麦片吧
You're eating Dyno-Bites
因为你还是个小屁孩
because you are a little boy.
老妈
Mom!
我告诉你  这孩子以后将会
I'm telling you, there's an embarrassing
面临一场难堪的记者招待会
press conference in that kid's future.
我们要在七个月后结婚
We're getting married in seven months.
或者八个月后
Or eight months.
我担心四月份总是阴雨绵绵
I worry about it raining in april.
我担心五月天热会出汗
Well, I worry about me sweating in may.
我们什么都定不下来
Oh, well, we can't decide on anything.
有  有太多选择了
There -- there are too many choices.
幸运的是  我们的一个好朋友
Fortunately, one of our best friends
是活动策划人
is an event planner.
-胡娇  -胡娇
- Pepper! - Pepper!
新郎驾到*
*Here come the grooms
身着我的胡娇系列无尾礼服*
*All dressed in fun tuxes from my Pepper collection
哇塞  瞧瞧你这一堆创意
Ha, wow -- look at all your ideas.
亲爱的  这些只是目录
Honey, this is just the index.
罗纳多
Ronaldo!
我带来了多种桌布  餐具
I brought linens and place settings
请帖  还有高脚杯
and invitations and stemware.
你们好  我是罗纳多
Hello. I'm Ronaldo.
别跟个话闸子似的
Oh, don't be such a chatterbox.
去把装餐盘的闸子拿来
And go and fetch the platter box.
把这张沙发拖走吧
Now, let's lose this couch.
你需要那么大地方吗
Wow, you need that much space, huh?
不是  因为太丑了
No, it's hideous.
这话你们肯定不是头一回听吧
This can't be news to you.
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
人人影视
YYeTs.com
■
翻译：小饭  猫中之王  慕秋雪  小牛仔裤  王大可  萌tu
时间轴：加森    校对：olivia_xuxu   后期&总监：瓜瓜
摩  登
家  庭
第五季 第六集
你毁了我的生活
You're ruining my life!
这鸡蛋很好吃啊
These eggs are delicious.
你有生活吗  从我的房间滚出去
What life?! Get out of my room!
我在里面加了牛奶
I put milk in them.
这已经不是你的房间了
It's not your room anymore!
口感非常松软
Well, they sure are fluffy.
妈
Mom!
-早上好老爸  -早上好  伙计们
- Hey, dad. - Morning, troops.
克莱尔  我欠你一盒女士剃刀
Claire, I owe you a pack of lady razors.
我要去院子里待一会儿
I'm just gonna go stand out in the yard.
真的  快滚出去
Seriously, get out!
我说过了  这不是你的房间
I told you it's not your room!
海莉跟艾丽克斯的关系
Tension between Haley and Alex
最近非常紧张
has been getting pretty high,
所以我们本来要让海莉搬到地下室
so our solution was to move Haley down to the basement,
但当我们刚打算实施时
which we were just about to do --
我爸爸来跟我们共度周末
When my dad came out for a weekend visit.
两周前就来了
Two weekends ago.
我妈妈去世后
After my mom passed away,
他开始跟名叫安妮的女人交往
he dated this woman named Annie,
后来她跟我爸分手
and she broke up with him,
我爸现在情绪有些低落
and then he seemed kind of down,
所以我邀他过来
so I invited him out.
太恶心了  那是我的袜子
Gross! Those are my socks!
才不是  妈
They are not! Mom!
我要出去待会儿
I'm just gonna pop outside.
我该给她买把耙子
I should get her a rake.
欢迎来到君临城
Welcome to King's landing!
我是邪恶的小国王
I am the evil boy king,
现在我要取了你们的首级
and I want your heads!
瞧瞧他们多喜欢你啊
Oh, look how much they all love you.
谢谢
Ohh, thanks.
我只是想跟孩子们的电子游戏
I'm just trying to match the energy
还有猜猜我是谁之类的游戏较较劲
of their video games and whosits and whatnots.
我要去打网球了
So, I'm gonna play tennis.
中午来接你
I can pick you up at noon.
-你好  你是琼对吧  -对
- Oh, hi! Joan, right? - Yes.
你好  我叫安迪
Hi. I'm Andy.
我是她的"曼尼"  就是男保姆的意思
I'm her manny -- male nanny.
你好  我叫歌洛莉亚
Hi, I'm Gloria.
我说这话可能有点神经质
This might just sound a little crazy,
但我觉得琼好像不喜欢我
but I don't think Joan likes me.
这不是神经质  她确实不喜欢你
Oh, that's not crazy. She doesn't.
她丈夫总是盯着你看
Her husband's always staring at you,
她担心你会抢了她老公
and she's worried you're gonna steal him.
-什么  -开心点  小家伙
- What?! - Be happy, little guy.
这个世界属于你
This world belongs to you.
我才不会抢别人的男人
I would never steal anybody else's man,
特别是她那个胖老公
especially not her fat husband.
他现在一点也不胖了
Hey, he's not fat anymore.
我帮他减了30磅
I helped him lose 30 pounds.
谢谢你  安迪
Thank you, Andy.
小心
Careful.
你要是受点小伤
If I bring you home scratched,
我的保证金就没了
I lose my deposit.
我略懂一些烹饪
I'm kind of a chef, too.
来  尝尝这个
Here, try this.
这是藜做的
It's quinoa.
消化它的过程就能消耗卡路里
You actually burn calories while eating I--
安迪  告诉我
So, Andy, tell me,
你在琼家干得开心吗
are you really happy with that Joan?
每场婚礼都别具一格  宛如每一片雪花
Every wedding is unique, like a snowflake.
而我的任务就是为你们
And my job is to give you
打造一片让每个人羡慕嫉妒恨的雪花
the snowflake that makes everyone die with jealousy.
我们要的就是这个效果
That's all we ever wanted.
那么我们先从配色开始吧
So, let's start with a color palette.
容我为你呈上
I'm thinking...
浓情深紫
Purple.
-深紫  这颜色还真是  -哇
- Purple! That is a color! - Wow!
我们不太  不太喜欢深紫
We don't love -- yeah, we don't love purple.
不是我们的最爱  不过
Not our favorite, but...
-什么  -深紫有点
- Excuse me? - Well, it's just that purple
太过火了
might be a little bit bold for --
不  我懂  你当我是白痴对吧
No, I get it. You think I'm an idiot.
-没有  -不是那个意思  胡娇
- No. No! - No, we don't, Pepper.
你俩显然比我在行多了
Well, obviously, you know better than I.
毕竟  我只帮人策划过
After all, I've only put on
数百场梦幻婚礼而已
hundreds of magnificent weddings.
走吧  罗纳多
Come, Ronaldo.
人家小两口不在乎婚礼策划
They're not interested in planning a wedding.
只喜欢糟蹋别人的心
They're interested in hurting people.
别走啊  胡娇  等一下
No, Pepper. Pepper, wait.
别这样  胡娇  听我说
No, Pepper, wait. Listen. No, no.
我们可以考虑一下深紫色
We can consider purple.
我们只是一下子接受不了而已
This is just a lot for us to take in.
那是自然  我明白了  我
Of course. I get it. I...
就让这个方案好好浸淫一下你们吧
Let the idea wash over you for a bit.
我们也可以考虑更素净的配色
We had also discussed a more neutral palette.
罗纳多  人家正浸淫着呢
Ronaldo! They're washing!
不好意思哦  他其实人不坏
I'm sorry. He means well.
现在  来谈谈你俩的出场方式
Now, let's talk about your entrance.
太好了  出场方式
Yes. Entrance.
两个男人能够共结连理
The idea of two men being able to marry
堪称是一场童话传奇
seemed like a fantasy,
所以我设想你俩是这样走上紫色长毯的
so I see you riding down the purple aisle
共同骑在一匹
on a...
独角兽上
...unicorn.
爷爷  你确定吗  会挺好玩的哦
Are you sure, grandpa? It might be fun.
抱歉  卢克  我今天实在没这个心情
Sorry, Luke. I just don't think I have it in me today.
你瞧见了没
Did you see that?
你爸什么时候
When has your dad ever
拒绝过和卢克玩拉手指放屁的游戏
not wanted to pull Luke's finger?
他心里难过着呢  菲尔
He's hurting, Phil.
他应该去看看心理医生
I think he needs to see a therapist.
克莱尔  我爸才不需要心理医生呢
Claire, he doesn't need a therapist.
为什么  老公  医生就是干这个的
Why? Honey, that's what they do.
专门帮人治疗情伤
They help people cope with loss.
如果实在需要  他们甚至会上门服务
They'll even come to the house if we need them to.
我应该请教一下我爸  知道吗
I should talk to my dad. You know what?
离婚之后他的心情也一度低沉
He was pretty down after the divorce.
-他肯定有办法  -是吗  因为你爸
- I bet he has some insight. - Yeah, 'cause your dad's
十分通情达理  善解人意吗
so in touch with people's feelings?
当人家被席琳・迪翁的演唱会
When a man is overcome with emotion
深深打动时
at a Celine Dion concert,
-他不该要人家硬气一点  -菲尔
- you do not tell him to grow a pair! - Phil!
泰坦尼克虽沉  人间真爱永存
The ship went down, but their love lasts forever!
老爸  你好啊
Dad? Hi.
我说  弗兰克最近心情不好
Yeah, listen. Uh, Frank is really depressed.
我觉得他应该找个心理医生
I think he should see a therapist.
-你觉得呢  -他才不需要那玩意呢
- What do you say? - He doesn't need any of that!
对吧  我也是这么说的
Yeah? Uh-huh. T-that's exactly what I said.
-电话给我  -我
- Give me that. - I-I...
杰  你刚才说什么
Jay, what did you just say?
带他出去  认识几个妹子
Take him out and meet some women.
一千个医生也抵不上歌洛莉亚对我的治疗
1,000 therapists couldn't do what Gloria did for me.
我同意  克莱尔她说错了
Oh, I agree. Claire was wrong.
告诉你  我知道个不错的地方
I'll tell you what. I know a fun place.
今晚  你我和弗兰克一起出去找点乐子
Tonight, you, me, and Frank out on the town.
太好了  我们三人行耶
Oh, fun! A three-way!
话一出口我已经后悔了
I already regret this.
我也很期待  不过我得先挂了
Well, I'm excited, too. I got to get going, though.
回见  拜
All right. Bye.
歌洛莉亚  我们回来了
Gloria, we're back!
来来来  让我帮你拿这个
Here! Let me lighten your load.
-你是谁呀  -我是新来的"曼尼"
- Who are you? - I'm the new manny.
你是来取代我的吗
Am I being replaced?
杰  曼尼  快来见见乔的新保姆安迪
Jay, Manny, meet Joe's new manny, Andy.
-我能借一步说话吗  -谢谢  不能
- Can I talk to you a second? -No, thank you.
我们应该好好商量一下这事
We're gonna need to discuss this.
我明白  这个决定事关重大
I get it. I understand it's a big decision.
如果能让你放心一点的话
But if it eases your mind at all,
我不光是来照顾宝宝乔的
know that I'm not just here for baby Joe.
我也是来照顾你们的
I'm here for you, too.
这话可一点没让我放心
Doesn't ease my mind at all.
我的任务就是让你们全家
My mission is to make all of your lives
过得更开心  活得更健康
happier and healthier.
难道是因为我吃掉了那条巨型三明治吗
Is this because I ate that party sub?
哎呀  该死
Ohh! Crackers!
我把电话落在育婴房里了
I left my phone upstairs in the nursery.
你能去帮我拿一下吗
Could you grab it for me?
我能理解人们在听到"健康"二字时
I know people get all squirrelly
做出的奇怪反应
when they hear the word "Healthy."
其实  曼尼  手机在我兜里呢
Actually, Manny? My phone is in my pocket.
不好意思  哥们
Sorry, bud.
我的目标是让你们在不经意间...
But my goal is to get you healthy without --
不对
Nope!
我兜里这个是一包口香糖
It is just a pack of gum.
手机还在楼上
My phone is still upstairs.
就变得健康起来
-- without you even realizing what's happening.
我真是后知后觉
Wow. I'm such a dodo.
我今天根本就没带手机
I didn't even bring my phone today.
我知道你在干什么
I know what you're doing.
这事我们得商量一下
We are gonna talk about it.
你有我的号码  我明天就可以开始工作
Okay, well, you have my number, so I can start tomorrow.
-打给我  -我会的
- Call me. - I will!
保重
Take care!
这个人不行  继续找吧
That's a nonstarter. Keep looking.
可是他很完美
But he's perfect.
他是男的  这很怪异
He's a man. It's weird.
他是个怪异的男人
He's a weird man.
就像菲尔  唯一区别是我还得付他钱
He's like Phil, only I have to pay for him.
家里不是某人独裁的  是民主的
This is not a dictatorship! It's a democracy!
投票决定
We vote!
不行  你总威吓曼尼让他屈服
No way. You always bully Manny, and he caves.
他很懦弱
He's weak.
无意冒犯
No offense.
所有觉得我们应该雇用安迪的人
Whoever thinks that we should hire Andy,
举手
raise the hand!
不行  对不起  妈妈  这回不行
No, sorry, mom. Not this time.
我不想在家里承受这种压力
I can't have that energy in my house.
好吧  那你们自己做饭吃吧
Fine. Cook your own dinner!
行  我们没问题
We will. We'll be fine.
那我们今晚吃什么
So, what are we having?
孩子  你得靠你自己  我今晚要出去
You're on your own, kid. I'm going out tonight.
你们觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
我喜欢这个
I like it.
不过  这个是不是有点儿像威利・旺卡
Also, is it a little Willy Wonka?
[《查理巧克力工厂》中的工厂主人]
你们一定是累了  我等明天
You're tired. I'll come back tomorrow
你们可以接受建设性意见的时候再来
when you're ready to be more constructive.
-胡娇  别走  -胡娇
- Pepper, no. - Pepper.
罗纳多  我们撤
Ronaldo, strike this.
抱歉  我还以为我今天穿着斗篷来的
Sorry. I thought I was wearing a cape today.
我的上帝
Oh. Oh, my gosh.
我们怎么办呐
Ohh. What are we gonna do?
我觉得我们得炒了胡娇
I-I think we have to fire Pepper.
他会伤心至死的
That would kill him.
-他已经在崩溃的边缘了  -怎么了
- He's on the brink as it is. - Why?
自从加州8号提案被推翻后
Since the proposition ocho was overturned,
[8号提案: 剥夺同性情侣结婚的权利]
他已经办了50场同性婚礼
he's done 50 gay weddings.
这男人为了新创意搜肠刮肚  耗尽心力
The man is exhausted, searching for new ideas.
你刚说了西语的"8"
You said "Ocho"
然后又说了英语的"50"
and then you said "50."
看到没  基佬们总是这么挑剔
You see? Gays are so nit-picky.
办异性婚礼
In a straight wedding,
你只要尽力讨好新娘就行了
you just have to please the bride,
但基佬们个个极具个性
But the gays have such strong opinions!
这让胡娇・萨尔茨曼这种伟大的
It takes a toll on a great artist
艺术家感到很受伤
like Pepper Saltzman.
我还从来没有从这个角度思考过
You know, I've never thought of it that way.
看看我们  我们自己都无法达成一致
I mean, look at us. We can't agree on one thing.
没错  你说得对
No, you're right.
小卡想要一种乡村风格的主题
I mean, Cam wants a rustic country theme,
而我则寻求一种
and I'm looking for something
略带现代感并精致的东西
a little more contemporary and sophisticated.
这根本就没法统一
And it's impossible.
但两种风格可以兼而有之
But you can have both.
写意的典雅  在经典的基础上略作改变
Casual elegance, classic with a twist.
继续说
Go on.
我会先用未经加工的天然亚麻长条桌布
I'd start with raw, natural-linen table runners
将两个世界连接在一起
to bring the two worlds together.
我们用带有农场特色的长方形桌面
We eschew the classic round tables
来避开经典圆形桌面的俗套
for rectangular farm tables,
但桌上的摆设要具有简洁的现代感
but keep the setting clean and modern.
然后
And then...
说啊
Yes!
不行  我不能这样  这样做不对
No, I mustn't. This is wrong.
胡娇是我的老板  我的良师
Pepper is my boss and my mentor!
他还是我们的朋友  我们在干什么
Oh, and he's our friend. What are we doing?
我们被迷惑了  我们没能抵抗住诱惑
We -- we got caught up. We gave in to temptation.
我得走了
I-I should go.
-别走  -我必须走
- Don't! - I must.
用复古的手绢给泪流成海的宾客拭泪
Vintage handkerchiefs for the guests to cry into.
罗纳多  等等
Ronaldo, wait!
用法式小酒馆那种带柄的红酒杯
French bistro stemless wine glasses.
我已经说了太多了
I've said too much.
罗纳多
Ronaldo!
他走了  小卡
He's gone, Cam.
伙计们  我们不能整晚都这么站着
Guys, we can't stand around all night.
我们总得找个人搭讪
At some point, we have to talk to somebody.
快点  那边那两位怎么样
Now, come on. How about those two?
我们过去吧
Let's go over there.
天呐  我不知道自己为什么这么紧张
Oh, my god. I don't know why I'm so nervous.
-你们好  女士们  -没兴趣
- Hello, ladies. - Not interested.
我不过打声招呼而已
Wow. I-I just said hello.
我们这是闺蜜间的小聚
We're just kind of having a girls' night.
凯西  友善些  我是玛希
Kathy, be nice. I'm marcy.
我是杰  这是弗兰克和菲尔
I'm Jay. This is Frank and, uh, Phil.
嗨好  我是想说你好  或者嗨
Hey-lo. I mean hey. Or hello.
我也不知道
I don't know.
声明一下  我只想给你们介绍我的朋友
And for the record, i just wanted to introduce my friend.
我可没想跟你搭讪或是怎样
I wasn't trying to pick you up or anything.
可真让我伤心
I'm heartbroken.
我们并不想打扰你们
We don't mean to disturb you.
你们没有打扰到我们
Oh, you're not disturbing us.
你的眼睛真漂亮
You have sweet eyes.
谢谢  我来自弗罗里达
Thank you. I'm from Florida.
我超爱弗罗里达的
I love Florida!
要不要坐下一起聊  弗兰克
Would you like to sit down, Frank?
这个嘛  好吧
Well, I, uh -- yeah, sure.
天啊  他真的要勾搭上女人了
Oh, my god. It's happening.
我告诉你  我老婆可是个大美女
For your information, I'm married to a gorgeous woman.
爸  杰和我
Dad, Jay and I
-去吧台买杯喝的  -没问题
- are gonna grab a drink from the bar. - Sure.
我手机里应该有她的照片
I think I have a picture of her here on this somewhere.
杰  我们走吧
Let’s go, Jay.
她还赢过选美大赛呢
Yeah, she won beauty pageants.
我可是很抢手的
Okay. I'm a catch.
我们赶紧走吧  这地方已经没意思了
Let's get out of here. This place is dead, anyway.
风流小子回家啦
Hey, there's Casanova!
我昨晚都没听见你回来
I didn't hear you come in last night.
你后来和玛希怎么样
So -- so, uh, how did it go with Marcy?
还行吧
Oh, it was okay.
但后来我打车的时候
But I actually met someone else
又遇到了别人
while I was waiting for a taxi.
是吗
Well, all right.
她现在就在楼下呢
And she's downstairs right now.
那好啊
Well, all right.
实际上  我碰上点小麻烦
Truth is, I, um, have a bit of a situation.
她说我欠她五百美金
She says I owe her $500.
拜托你告诉我这是因为你弄伤了她
Please tell me you broke something of hers.
不是  原来她是个妓女
No, turns out she's a hooker.
你找了个妓女
You picked up a hooker?
我当时不知道她是妓女
Well, I didn't know she was a hooker.
别在我家厨房里再提"妓女"这个词了
We're in my kitchen. We have to stop saying "Hooker"!
你得在克莱尔练瑜伽回来前
You got to get her out of here
把那女的弄出去
before Claire gets back from yoga.
不给钱她就不走
She's not gonna leave until she gets the cash.
五百美金吗  你被坑了吧
$500? I think you got ripped off.
-喝口你的咖啡成吗  -好吧
- Hey, can I have a hit of that coffee? - Oh, that's fine.
相信我  我绝对没坑他
Trust me. He did not get ripped off.
没事  你留着吧
No, that's good. It's yours.
这只有247块  我还得去取钱
$247. I'm gonna have to run to an atm.
你怎么会没看出来呢
How could you not know?!
又喝酒呀又调戏呀
Well, the drinks, the flirting.
就有点晕晕乎乎的嘛
I couldn't think straight.
你有没有摸过48岁女人的
Have you ever touched the smooth,
光滑柔软的皮肤
taut skin of a 48-year-old woman?
我希望有一天能摸到
I hope to one day,
但要是克莱尔回来发现...
but that's not gonna happen if Claire gets home and --
我回来啦
Hi! I'm back!
弗兰克  昨天晚上玩得爽吗
Frank, did you have fun last night?
不  一点儿都不爽
No. He did not.
厨房里那女的是谁啊
Hey. Who's the woman in the kitchen?
我哪儿知道  我去洗脸刷牙了
Beats me. I think I'll go freshen up.
厨房里有个女的吗
There's a woman in the kitchen?
对  是有个女的  她是个心理医生
There's a woman in the kitchen. Yeah, she's a therapist.
就是你推荐我爸看的心理医生
The therapist that you recommended.
我觉得是个好主意
So I decided it was a good idea.
你能接受我的建议我真是太开心了
Oh, that means the world that you listened to me.
-你真贴心  -要不你先洗个澡
- Thank you! - Ohh, you should get a shower upstairs.
不  我要去打个招呼
Oh, no, I want to say hi.
你浑身都是汗
No, not sweaty like that.
一身臭汗味
You smell.
别这样
No, uh...
你好  我是克莱尔
Hi! Hi, I'm Claire.
我是弗兰克的儿媳妇
I'm Frank's daughter-in-law,
我就是想感谢你
and I just want to thank you so much
过来这样帮助了他
for coming and helping him out this way.
-这是我出的主意  -不是的
- It was my idea. - No, it wasn't.
-好吧  -行了
- Okay. - All right.
我从没和别人说起过
No, hey. I've never told anyone this,
但我一直想从事你的工作
but I have always wanted to do what you do.
我觉得我会挺在行的
I think I'd be really good at it.
-不  她不会的  -你说什么呢
- No, she wouldn't. - What are you talking about?
我本来也已经在这样造福全社区了
It's basically what I already do for the whole neighborhood.
像你这样的话我还能挣点钱
At least this way, I get paid for it.
我十点半还有约  我得走了
You know, I got a standing 10:30 I got to get to.
-是得走  快走  -妈  我要吐了
- Yes. Yes, you do! - Mom, I'm gonna throw up!
艾丽克斯的头发闻起来像奶酪
Alex’s hair smells like cheese!
不是奶酪
It is not cheese!
是不用动物做实验的有机洗发水
It is cruelty-free organic shampoo
里面加了一些搅拌过的羊奶
with traces of churned goat's milk!
所以就是奶酪
So cheese!
恶心死了  给我个桶来吐一下
Ew, I need a bucket!
女孩们  家里有客人
Ladies, we have a guest.
真是对不起
I am -- I'm really sorry about this.
我就是拿她们两个没办法
I'm just at my wit's end with these two.
你有没有处理青年人的经验啊
I don't suppose you have any experience with teenagers?
别说了
Oh, no.
你们两个让我想起我和我妹妹
You two remind me of me and my sister.
我们以前总是吵架
We used to fight all the time.
我说她抢我男友
I used to accuse her of stealing my boyfriend.
她说我要把她捅死
She would accuse me of trying to stab her.
-就是姐妹那些事儿  -天哪
- You know, sister stuff. - Oh, my god.
相信我  老娘要是想捅死她
Trust me, if I wanted to stab her,
那骚货早就被捅死了
that skank be stabbed.
她不是心理医生对吗
She's not a therapist, is she?
别听了
Just...
我就没怎么合眼
I didn't sleep a wink.
我无法控制自己不去想罗纳多
I-I cannot stop thinking about Ronaldo.
我也是
I know.
我梦见我们的婚礼登上
I dreamt our wedding made
《摩登同性婚礼》杂志封面了
the cover of Modern Gay Grooms
还梦见确实有《摩登同性婚礼》这本杂志
and that there was a magazine called Modern Gay Grooms.
是胡娇
Okay, that's -- that's Pepper.
就跟他说让罗纳多来主持策划好了
Let's just ask him to let Ronaldo take the lead.
然后承担伤害胡娇的风险么
And -- and risk hurting Pepper?
可是据我们所知
For all we know,
罗纳多根本不想为了我们背叛胡娇
Ronaldo hasn't even given us a second thought.
我无法控制自己不去想你们
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
昨天这里发生的一切都是真情实意
What happened here yesterday was real.
罗纳多  我们也感受到了
Oh, Ronaldo! We felt it, too.
但胡娇怎么办
But what about Pepper?
-我离开他了  -什么
- I left him. - What?
都结束了  他不像你们这样看重我
It's over. He doesn't look at me the way you do.
这一切来得太突然了
Ohh, this is all happening so fast.
我也这样觉得
For me, too.
但昨天离开时我的心跳得好快
But my heart was racing when I left here.
你们是我的缪斯女神
You are my muses-es.
我感觉好内疚
Ohh. I feel so guilty.
快速瞟一眼  没人会知道
One quick look. No one has to know.
罗纳多  你都做了些什么
Oh, Ronaldo, what have you done?
米奇尔  卡梅隆
Mitchell! Cameron!
-天哪  -快  藏起来
- Oh, no! - Uh, uh, quick! Hide!
好的  我藏起来
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I'll hide.
-小卡  不是你  -快进去  快去
- Cam, not you. - Okay, yeah. Go, go, go, go, go.
罗纳多离开我了
Ronaldo left me.
-什么  不可能  -那个小人
- What?! No! - The swine!
有人告诉他说  他没了我也照样能行
Someone put it in his head that he could do this without me.
但是你们听好了  我会毁了他
But mark my words, I will destroy him
毁了那个他在筹办的婚礼
and whatever wedding he thinks he's planning.
好吧  那是一种办法
Okay, well, that's one way to go.
大爸二爸  洗手间有个人
Daddies, there's a man in the bathroom.
-什么  -那是首儿歌
- What? - That -- that's a Wiggles song.
是首儿歌
That's a Wiggles song.
爸爸  洗手间有个人*
*Daddy, there's a man in the bathroom
洗手间有个人*
*There's a man in the bathroom
没事的宝贝  没事
It's okay, honey. It's okay.
他在洗澡*
*He's in the shower
在我发掘他以前  罗纳多什么都不是
Ronaldo was nothing before I found him,
住在一个比这里大不了多少的垃圾堆里
living in squalor in a dump barely bigger than this.
他怎么能这样对我
How could he do this to me?
因为你从来都听不进去别人的话
Because you never listen to anybody!
我有好的点子  但你却笨到听不进去
I have good ideas, but you're too thick-headed to hear them!
罗纳多  你怎么在这里
Ronaldo, how did you get here?
是你们俩  你们两个暗算我
It was you two. You plotted against me.
刚才那根本不是儿歌  对不对
I bet that's not even a Wiggles song, is it?
-对不对  -不是
- Is it?! - No.
胡娇  我们可以解释
Pepper, we can explain.
你们知道我有多努力吗
Do you have any idea how hard I work?
也许那正是你的问题之一
Well, maybe that's part of the problem.
我是说  你饱尝辛酸  胡娇
I mean, you've been through the mill, Pepper.
别吐槽
Heard it.
我策划过53场同性婚礼
I've done 53 gay weddings.
没有一场是我自己的
And... none of them are mine.
胡娇
Ohh. Pepper.
这又是谁的错呢
And whose fault is that?
你好像在说这是我的错
I feel like you're implying mine,
但我真的不这么认为
but I really don't see it.
一个如此会布置餐桌的人
How can a man with such flare for setting tables
怎么会不给爱他的人留个位置呢
leave no seat for one who loves him?!
-天哪  -罗纳多爱上胡娇了
- Oh, my god. - Ronaldo's in love with Pepper.
对啊  所以我才说"天哪"
I know. That's why I said, "Oh, my god."
胡娇  你听到罗纳多说的话了么
Pepper, do you hear what Ronaldo is saying?
当然听到了  我又不是傻子
Of course I do. I'm not a fool.
他认为我不会布置餐桌
He thinks I can't set a table.
不  不不不
No. No, no, no.
罗纳多爱上你了  快过去
Ronaldo is in love with you. Go to him.
什么
What?
你爱上我了
You're in love with me?
是的  是真的
Si. It is true. Yes.
天哪  那会让我疯掉的
God, that would drive me crazy.
罗纳多  我不知该说什么
Ronaldo, I-I don't know what to say.
当然  我雇你的时候
I mean, of course, when I hired you,
我认为你很有吸引力
I found you very attractive.
那是我雇佣任何一个人的原因
That's why I hire all my people.
但我
But I...
我从没想过
I never thought you...
你会认为我...
would find me...
很完美吗
Perfecto?
因为你就是那样的  完美无暇
Because that's what you are -- perfect.
不  我走了  走了  受不了了
No. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I can't.
歌洛莉亚  我忘拿毛巾了
Gloria, I forgot my towel!
给  热气腾腾刚烘干的
Here it is. Nice and toasty from the dryer.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
她去买东西了  早餐五分钟就好
She ran to the store. Breakfast in 5.
内裤已经熨好并放在你床上了
Your underpants are pressed and on your bed.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
所以  如果我理解得没错的话
So, if I'm hearing you right, you're not so much mad
比起厨房里的妓女
about the prostitute in the kitchen
你更为我对你说谎而生气
as you are about my lying to you.
不  我生气是因为厨房里有个妓女
No, I'm mad about the prostitute in the kitchen.
那是我的错
Hmm. That's my bad.
是的  是你的错  弗兰克  非常错
Yes, it is. It's your bad, Frank. Very bad.
听着  我是一个进步女性
Look, I'm a progressive woman.
我上过钢管舞课程
I-I took a pole-dancing class.
我送女儿去大学时会给她带避孕套
I sent my daughter to college with condoms.
等等  我认为那样反而会让她产生误解
Wait, now, I think that sends the wrong message.
-多谢支持  -你没资格评论
- Thank you very much. - No! You don't get to judge!
我  弗兰克  我
I...Frank, I'm --
我知道安妮和你分手让你很伤心
I know you're upset about Annie breaking up with you.
等等  安妮没有和我分手
Wait, Annie didn't break up with me.
是我提的分手
I broke up with her.
-什么  -为什么  她不是很好吗
- W-what? - Why? I thought she was so great!
我感到很恐惧  我不知道应该怎么
Well, I got scared. I didn't know how to...
和另一个女人相处
be with another woman.
我曾以为会永远和你母亲在一起
I thought your mother and I would be together forever.
我很遗憾  老爸
Ah... I'm sorry, dad.
我从没想过要发生昨晚这样的事
I never would have gone through with it last night,
但是  珍妮人很好  很专业
but, uh, Jeannie was so nice and professional.
谢谢你了  弗兰克
Well, thank you, Frank.
还有  不得不说
And for what it's worth,
你没有什么好担心的
you got nothing to be nervous about.
你很棒
You were wonderful.
真的  你真的这么认为
Really? You think so?
真的
Yeah.
如果你爱那个女人  就去把她追回来
If you love that woman, you should go get her back.
她和你在一起会很幸福
She'll be lucky to have you.
真的  我见过很多你这个年龄的
Seriously, I see a lot of guys your age.
大部分几乎都
Most of them can barely --
行了  我们送你上出租车
Okay. Let's get you in that cab.
我超爱你家小孩
I love your kids.
艾丽克斯跟我小时候超像
That Alex is like a little me.
-是吗  -我的老天爷啊
- Yeah! - Oh, My God.
早上好  老板  小老板
Good morning, boss, junior boss.
坐下尝尝这个
Grab a seat and check it out.
煎蛋清卷  高蛋白奶昔
Egg-white omelet, high-protein smoothies,
吃完我们可以穿上运动鞋去
then I thought we could put on our running shoes and go...
不得不打断你  朋友
I need to cut you off right there, chief.
看来是我妻子越界了
Seems my wife overstepped her bounds.
-你看起来是个好小伙  -谢谢
- Now, you seem like a nice guy. - Thanks.
但我并不认为你适合在我家干活儿
But I don't think you're the best fit for this house.
-你  你是认真的吗  -恐怕是的
- Are -- are you serious? - I'm afraid so.
好吧
Okay.
是因为我给你熨了内裤  是吗
It was the underpants, wasn't it?
有这个原因
That didn't help.
我做得太过了  该死
Man, I came on too strong. Gosh dang it!
在我14岁时我爸就警告过我
My dad warned me about that when I turned 14.
他说  "孩子  你将成为一家之主
He said, "Son, you're about to be the man of the family.
你得给别人一些时间
You got to learn to give people time
来看到你的好"
to see how special you are."
为什么你是一家之主
Why were you the man of the family?
-他去世了  -因为什么呢
- He sort of died. - How?
我不想让你不开心  小鬼
I don't want to bring you down, little man.
我爸当初也一样
Neither did my dad.
他说  "我的病和'答案'的发音押韵
He'd say, "My disease can't be all bad
因此也不全是坏事"
if it rhymes with 'answer.'"
我烤的亚麻籽松饼好了
Those are the flaxseed muffins that I just baked.
我把它们拿出来就走
I'll just take them out and get out of here.
安迪  等等
Andy, wait.
我们不会吃的
We're never gonna eat them.
那么  好吧  抱歉我没有做好
Well, then... I'm sorry it didn't work out.
什么没做好
What didn't work out?
我在这里的使命
My mission here.
真的很高兴认识你  普夫人
It was really nice to meet you, though, Mrs. P.
你连一个机会都不给他
You didn't even give him a chance.
我们投过票了的  妈妈
We took a vote, mom.
你得尊重投票
You got to respect the vote.
不  你让我雇那些我不喜欢的保姆
No! You make me hire these nannies that I don't like.
现在我找到一个喜欢的  你又要辞了他
But when I find one that I like, you fire him?!
我才是在这屋子里花时间最多的人
I am the one that spends most of the time around here!
所以该由我来决定
SO I GET TO PICK!
有些时候我们的声音越大  越不被理解
Sometimes the louder we are, the less we're heard.
-你现在很沮丧  对吗  -没错
- You're frustrated right now, aren't you? - Yes.
因为你觉得他们不理解你
Because you feel like they're not hearing you.
没错
Yes.
这也正是他们的感受
Well, that's exactly how they feel.
抱歉我忽略了你们的感受
I'm sorry that I ignored your feelings.
我保证不会再这样咆哮了
I promise that I will try not to yell so much.
-你被录用了  -什么
- You're hired. - What?!
你最好喝了那奶昔  我们要去跑步了
You better drink that smoothie. We're going on a run!
这事儿还没完
This isn't over.
生活并不容易
Life isn't easy.
有时我们只是需要一点点帮助
Sometimes we just need a little help,
来重拾自信
getting your confidence back,
来达成一致
getting on the same page,
来释放自己
getting out of your own way,
或者就是运动起来
or just getting moving.
我很高兴来做这个帮手
And I'm pleased as punch to be the one --
够了  你不念叨都够累了
Okay, this is tough enough without all the yammering!
抱歉
Sorry.
你想要什么伴舞音乐
What would you like to dance to?
我得告诉你  我们要跳方块舞
I have to tell you we have to have some sort of square dancing.
不要放乡村音乐
We're not doing country.
不要方块舞  不要
No square dancing. We're not.
今晚不会有方块舞舞会  胡娇和我
There will be no hoedown tonight. Pepper and I are on...
我的家人会大发脾气
My family is going to throw a fit.
-他们会捣乱  -我们不是为他们而婚
- They'll riot. - We're not getting married for them.
我们是为自己结婚
We're getting married for us.
我觉得我们应该有一个多层裱花蛋糕
And I think we have a decorative cake out front,
再在后面放一个单层蛋糕
and then we have sheet cakes in the back.
我知道你想要什么主题了
Oh, I see! Is that the theme you're going for
土气主题
-- tacky?!
"单层的"  像床单那样铺开的
Sheet -- like a sheet.
"单层的"啊
Oh, "Sheet."
我还以为你说的是"花哨的"
I thought he said "Chic cake."
我的蛋糕都很花哨
All of my cakes are chic.